{
    "id": "04c4ca6ab0de4862a09af99e8e49e58f",
    "title": "See, Look And Watch",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Ring up and .................................. whether she is at home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "look",
                "watch"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "65dfe22526fd4a52990e979634a1c5f9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................................... a dark figure behind the window.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "watched",
                "looked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a66579eea3744275b72e3224a30e26ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly I ........................................ something strange.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "watched",
                "looked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c1ac3551dbff4f9a886286f2b66da206"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please ........................................ at this photo.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watch",
                "see",
                "look"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "948638824f3b43a98198feff9316380d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you ........................................ that man in the blue shirt?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "watch",
                "look"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c7fe2b389f594663b49e15b34291ef7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... what you have done.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "See",
                "Watch",
                "Look"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e15ff04dcfb84b7b9ef1feea5524ffac"
        },
        {
            "question": "I like to ..................................... football matches on TV.",
            "description": "Either see or watch is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "watch",
                "look"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d10898e8da6348ac809d534046f038de"
        },
        {
            "question": "That kid spends too much time .................................. TV.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "seeing",
                "watching",
                "looking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9a6c525f9df6419b924d09b2e682369a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Iâ€™m looking to ................................. whether there is any food left.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "look",
                "watch"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c0a66f84360c469ba54464cda727130d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................... they are going to put up taxes again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "look",
                "see",
                "watch"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bb2f8fc14751438198aadc977b696b7a"
        }
    ]
}